Raymond Reynolds

123 Alphabet Street, Oakland, CA 12345 r.reynolds@ernail.com (123) 123-1234

Car salesperson with 13+ years of experience selling numerous makes and models. Plans and executes successful promotional deals. Has a proven history of impressing new prospects and following up to build customer relationships. A diligent communicator who works with other parties, including the finance team, to seal deals.

Key Skills

- Customer service
- ♦ Vehicle descriptions
- Negotiations
- Coordination with other dealership employees

Professional Experience

Senior Sales Consultant

Oakland Hyundai-Nissan, Oakland, CA I December 2016 - Present

- Discuss customers' needs and guide them through the sales process, maintaining a 95% customer satisfaction score and beating quarterly sales targets by an average of \$30,000
- Accompany customers on test drives, collecting identification and insurance information beforehand
- Educate customers regarding features, maintenance needs, standard equipment, and special feature packages
- Negotiate deals respectfully and follow up with customers after sales, boosting repeat customer rate by 10% to date
- Suggest promotion ideas to sales manager and, with approval, oversee and execute one promotion per quarter

Sales Consultant

San Francisco Ford, San Francisco, CA I July 2008 - November 2016

- Greeted walk-in customers and appointment arrivals at the door
- Interviewed customers and recommended Ford sedans, trucks, and SUVs based on their needs
- Handled negotiations and liaised with the finance team to secure financing for customers
- Upsold warranties and maintenance packages, outperforming average team upsell rate by 15%

Education

Associate's Degree in Sales and Marketing

Bay Area Community College, Palo Alto, CA, September 2004 - June 2008

Certifications

♦ Auto Sales Association Certified Car Sales Professional, 2017